export const Questions = [{
        prompt: "1.Which mean of transport is used on the ground?",
        optionA: "car",
        optionB: "plane",
        optionC: "ship",
        optionD: "two ships",
        answer: "car",
        number: "1",
    },
    {
        prompt: "2. What was the original color for all Ferrari models?",
        optionA: "red",
        optionB: "blue",
        optionC: "white",
        optionD: "purple",
        answer: "red",
        number: "2",
    },
    {
        prompt: "3.Which iconic car manufacturer also made airplane engines?",
        optionA: "Rolls Royce",
        optionB: "Mercedes",
        optionC: "BMW",
        optionD: "Fiat",
        answer: "Rolls Royce",
        number: "3",
    },
    {
        prompt: "4.Who was a driver for Alpha Romeo before founding his own company?",
        optionA: "Enzo Ferrari",
        optionB: "Martin Fabisiak",
        optionC: "Kaczyński",
        optionD: "Tusk",
        answer: "Enzo Ferrari",
        number: "4",
    },
    {
        prompt: "5. Who designed the Volkswagen Beetle?",
        optionA: "Ferdinand Porsche",
        optionB: "Segal",
        optionC: "Bruce Willis",
        optionD: "Dicaprio",
        answer: "Ferdinand Porsche",
        number: "5",
    },
    {
        prompt: "6. In which year did Henry Ford establish the Ford Motor Company?",
        optionA: "1903",
        optionB: "1904",
        optionC: "1905",
        optionD: "1906",
        answer: "1903",
        number: "6",
    },
    {
        prompt: "7. Which sports car features in the Back To The Future trilogy?",
        optionA: "DeLorean",
        optionB: "Fiat",
        optionC: "BMW",
        optionD: "VW",
        answer: "DeLorean",
        number: "7",
    },
    {
        prompt: "8. What does Volkswagen mean?",
        optionA: "The ‘people’s car’",
        optionB: "car",
        optionC: "ship",
        optionD: "plane",
        answer: "The ‘people’s car’",
        number: "8",
    },
    {
        prompt: "9. What is the best-selling electric car in history?",
        optionA: "The Tesla Model 3",
        optionB: "BMW",
        optionC: "Mercedes",
        optionD: "Fiat",
        answer: "The Tesla Model 3",
        number: "9",
    },
    {
        prompt: "10. Which race car is known as the widow maker?",
        optionA: "Porsche 917",
        optionB: "BMW",
        optionC: "Ferrari",
        optionD: "Mercedes",
        answer: "Porsche 917",
        number: "10",
    },
]